Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
When will the raft come to
take us, Andreas?
According to Lord Rogatos' messenger,
they should have come already, sir Grego.
Soldiers!
We'll take Father Gregor and return to the
castle with the order of Lord Rogatos!
I don't want any trouble!
My Alps!
With Allah's permission,
we are going to...
fly like an eagle,
take Father Gregor and...
return to our land.
- Inshallah my Bey.
There, there he is, sir
Father Gregor.
Bilecik's Lord Rogatus sent me
to take you.
Nice, nice.
My friend Rogatus.
Lord Rogatus' loyal soldiers are waiting
for you.
Here.
Come.
God bless you, son.
Here.
Come, here.
We'll wait here.
Let's see when they'll fall into
our clutches.
- Baysungur.
- My Bey.
You know what to do.
I know, my Bey.
Go.
My dear friend.
Where are we going?
Where exactly are Feodor and
his loyal soldiers waiting for us?
They are waiting for you Goksu front, sir.
Interesting.
They were supposed to wait for us
around Cakirca.
I think we were mistaken.
Here one of the murderers of his relative,
Michael Kosses...
while we are running away from the Emperor.
Or should I have said
Inegol Lord Aya Nicola?
Search him.
So you are a Turk.
You'll drown.
You'll eat in hell!
The rift is going somewhere else.
Not here.
Cerkutay...
is not on the rift, my Bey.
Let's go!
Catalans!
Deploy!
Do not show mercy!
Bring Father, kill the rest!
Damn it!
Where did they come from?
For the Lasgaris dynasty!
There was supposed to be only Rogatus!
- Is this for the Emperor, sir Gregor?
- I don't know, Andreas!
Father Gregor.
You maniac!
Where is the Father?
Are you asking me, Diego?
You were supposed to get him while
I was fighting, Diego!
Father Gregor...
From now on, you are in hands of Osman Bey,
the son of Kayi Bey Ertugrul Ghazi.
I've heard your name.
All the east churches damned you for what
you've done to the sons of Jesus, Osman Bey.
I'll give you a chance to let you see
the outcome of your prayers.
Kill me if you are going to kill me.
I am not afraid of you.
I am not afraid of dying at all!
That's fine!
Don't worry.
We'll take care of your goods
and your life.
Alps.
Get him in the tent in secret.
- Eyvallah(okay) my Bey.
Bilecik Castle.
I want a cloak out of brocade...
Silas.
It must be processed with gold thread.
I don't want a thick frame.
Two-inch-thick is okay.
There will be a griffon drawing on it.
Oh no, no.
Two griffons looking at each other.
What a beautiful description this is!
Don't worry sir.
We are going to make it as you want.
You know, Silas...
I always respected tailoring.
It's a subtle job.
Very subtle.
However, I don't have that ability.
Sir...
Take them off.
Take them off and get out.
Feodor?
What is up with you?
And of course, where is Father Gregor?
I don't know sir.
We couldn't get him.
You couldn't get him?
Where are your soldiers?
I mean, do you have any left, Feodor?
Tell me what happened there!
C-Catalans...
Catalans sir.
Catalans.
Catalans, huh?
God damn dogs!
For whom Catalans abducted Father Gregor?
They were like waiting for this moment
for years.
My soldiers were not young and
inexperienced. We were not afraid.
We were not afraid, but...
Shut up already!
Catalans have one of the most important
man of God...
... my friend and relative Father Gregor...
... and you are still making up a story!
Someone else took Gregor.
Damn it!
There was someone else.
They were from Bithynia.
That snake must have wrested Father Gregor
off while you were busy with Catalans.
Kosses!
If Kosses has...
...Father Gregor...
...Catalans?
Who are they working for?
For the Emperor?
We are going to figure that out from
Kosses in Nicola's invitation.
Harmankaya Castle.
What is happening, Nestor?
What is this hurry about?
Sir, your sister Mari...
departed from Constantine.
Excellent!
That is good news!
Get out.
Nothing about that damned Jhanselno?
Sir, Catalan Anselmo wants to see you.
This smell...
is the smell of losers.
Anselmo.
This smell is the smell of a silly soldier
who couldn't keep his promise!
This smell is the smell of a corpse...
Anselmo.
As you know, a piece good information
brings victory.
You informed us wrongly!
The whole Bithynia was there
to get the Father!
We lost the Father.
"Wrong information"?
"The whole Bithynia was there."
Do not give me that story, Anselmo.
We made an agreement. I promised you gold
in return for Father Gregor.
I paid you half.
If you win, you win.
If you lose, you lose. again.
Anselmo doesn't lose.
I didn't come all the way from Catalonia.
I'll find Gregor and bring him to you.
I'll get what I want in return.
I am a loyal man to my agreement.
Bring me the Father, get your gold.
You don't even know who has the Father.
We should send our men everywhere, sir.
Everywhere?
Very clever.
I'm invited to Nikola's dinner tonight.
Let's see what will we learn from the
eyes of our 'friendly' lords.
Make your preparations, Mestor.
Bring back your mind, soul
and ideas...
that you left there, in Catalonia!
Or else you will return your home
empty-handed.
I don't lose, he says.
Incompetent.
Thank you, ladies.
Inshallah he'll have a long life
to grow a beard as white as flour.
Amin.
Inshallah he'll have a tongue as
sweet as honey.
Wheat is prosperity, may his
prosperity never end.
Inshallah, his life will be as
clean as salt.
Thank you, Selcan Mother. You doubled
our happiness with your arrival.
Thank you, daughter.
Malhun Hatun is right, mother.
You livened up the tribe.
My pretty girl.
Longing is difficult.
I missed all of you.
Come, ladies. Come.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy it.
Bala?
Are you alright?
I'm fine. I'm fine. I just
got a weird smell.
-Here, Bala.
-Thank you.
May Allah destine you with a long
and glorious life.
May you have a good family.
May Allah protect you from
the evil.
May you be destined to be a worthy
child of your ancestors.
Your Selcan Mother loves you.
My pretty child.
Bala Hatun, you don't look well.
I brought you thymus juice.
What's wrong, my girl?
I'm fine, mother.
I'm fine.
-Here, Malhun.
-Thank you, Gökçe.
Bala!
Come, let's take a walk.
It'll do you good.
-If you allow us.
-Of course, my daughter.
If you allow us.
Ayşe, my girl.
Draw it over.
Who is this girl?
I haven't seen her before.
It's Gökçe.
Ever since Alaca married and left,
she accompanies me.
Good, then. She is skillful.
It shows.
Bala, what are you doing?
You can't drink thymus juice
when you are pregnant.
I don't know, Gonca.
I forgot about it.
Come on, Bala. Please.
Be careful.
What about now?
Are you feeling better?
I'm fine.
I'm fine, Gonca.
Be fine, Bala. Be fine.
But be careful.
Now you carry two lives.
Come.
You are in a great struggle.
I say that this is your biggest
hunt so far.
Catholic and Orthodox fires can
drop on Söğüt any time.
Are we strong enough to
bear this struggle?
In the lands of Anatolia, Turks are
shattered into a thousand pieces.
The Islamic world is fighting over
Shiism and Sunnism.
For this reason, if we are
divided...
they can't be united either.
They will divide too.
They won't unite.
They won't dream about us.
They will have sleepless nights.
They will pay the price...
for every innocent Muslim they killed.
Let them run after us now...
let them try to find a way out now.
My sheik, I'll gain Father Gregor's
trust first.
He and the whole Orthodox people
will see that the Pope isn't the savior.
It's Ottomans who fly
the flag of justice.
Mashallah.
May your sword be sharp,
your heart be brave.
As long as your heart
is devoted to this...
every difficulty can be
taken care of.
Inshallah, my sheik.
Cerkutay can't die.
Lovers can't die.
I can't, Kumral Abdal.
-It's the only reason.
-Stop havering.
Mashallah, you have nine lives.
You can't stop it because
you are healed.
You will drink these
forever.
Thank you, Kumral Abdal.
Mashallah, back then...
you healed hearts with
your words...
now, you spread healing
with your skillful hands.
Sush! What skill?
Don't say such things again!
My Allah! Everyone has
wise people around them...
I only attract crazy people
or traitors.
Give me patience, my Allah.
There are important news.
Tell me, Gökçe.
What is it?
I eavesdropped on Bala and
Gökçe Hatun.
-Bala Hatun is pregnant.
-Pregnant?
My Allah...
My Allah, what a difficult
test is this?
I was the ornament of Umur Tribe.
I was the dearie of my father.
I accepted to be the second
wife of a brave man...
only because his first wife
couldn't get pregnant.
I wanted the tribes to be united.
I wanted the Turks to be united.
''If I'll have a child, let it be
from Osman Bey.''
My Allah...
Why did they hide it?
Are they...
My son...
What if it's a boy?
İnegöl Castle
Dear Rogatos!
How are you?
You should ask yourself.
You don't look well.
It's a terrible day.
Maybe it's not the day but
your perspective?
Because your terrible day might
be a glorious one for another, right?
Behold!
Nikola, the lord of İnegöl!
Magnificus!
He thinks he is Caesar.
Finally, my friends. Finally!
Kosses!
You are solid as a rock, like always.
Rogatos!
You have foxes in your head again.
Our friend is having a terrible day.
I know.
Come.
Rogatos' close friend and relative,
Gregor...
have escaped from the emperor's
dungeon.
And someone took him on his
way to Rogatos.
Did I get it right?
You want to protect a traitor who is
wanted by Emperor Andronicus.
Is this right, Rogatos?
Aren't you afraid?
Father Gregor might be
a traitor for now.
But this is life, he might turn
into a hero tomorrow.
My old friend loves protecting
heroes.
''They are the agents of Jesus
on earth.
Those who protect them will accompany
Jesus in heaven.''
Rogatos, you sound like someone
who wants to be a saint.
But, know this...
I will find out where
Father Gregor is.
And when I do, I will take him.
If only you knew...
how much I would like to
have that Father.
Dear, Rogatos.
But unfortunately, I don't have him.
Otherwise, I would like you to
be with Jesus in heaven.
Yes.
If none of us have Gregor...
then, who has him?
Of course, Osman is our primary
suspect.
Osman, the Bey of the Kayı.
The one that you always fail to beat...
Right, Nikola?
Master Gregor, what will we do now?
We wanted to flee from the emperor,
now we are in the hands of the heathens.
-Was it all for this?
-Your fuss won't help us, Andreas.
You need to be calm.
Will we stay idle, Master Gregor?
If we know why we are here,
we can find a way out of here.
How did Osman know about us?
How did he know that we were coming?
May your evening be good, Father.
Your words are sweet but your power
is keeping us captive.
This evil can only be expected
by a man like you.
Captivity is difficult.
I know it well.
I was tortured in your dungeons.
But let's not call this
captivity.
We are hosting you.
So, it's our destiny to spend time
in the heart of the devil.
What I wonder is, how has that
devil heard of us?
How does the devil know us?
You fleed from the devil's lap,
Father.
You wouldn't be here if you were brave
against that devil...
who imprisoned you, who blinded
the Patriarch.
You know everything.
I know how the Byzantine Emperor...
gave you and the Patriarch orders,
to unite the Orthodoxes and Catholics...
for the Pope's support.
I know how the Patriarch was blinded
for refusing.
I know how they tortured you
in that dungeon.
And I know...
how eager you were
to escape there.
I know how you fought like
a man, too.
You deserved heaven, my loyal
friend.
You will be reborn with Christ's
companions. Give me your name.
The secret is revealed, sir.
The secret is revealed.
If you reveal the secret,
you know everything, Father.
-What do you want from us?
-Just like this.
Now, listen to me.
Osman kidnapping the Father
doesn't sound possible to me.
But you know him better, Nikola.
You've seen him in battles.
Tell us now.
What kind of a man is Osman?
Osman...
how could he know our internal affairs
that he can know the Father?
If Osman sees the greatness of his
prey...
he'll turn into a Father, a shepherd
anything, Rogatos.
My God. It's been a while...
since we faced the enemy but...
I didn't know that Osman turned into
such a dangerous devil.
I do.
After all, you left me all alone
in this war, Kosses.
I waved the Byzantine flag
alone.
But you fought and fought to
be Caesar, Nikola.
Understand it, this isn't Rome.
A bit of love, a bit of wine...
a bit of trade. Am I wrong?
You don't understand.
Osman is growing,
in lands...
in people, in power...
He is growing!
Soon, he'll turn into a snake that will
eat us all!
If we don't unite...
we'll all vanish soon.
Then...
We'll strengthen our unity.
But Osman shouldn't see or hear
us.
He should think that we
have a problem.
Otherwise, Osman will...
make us fight each other with
his devilry.
For Byzantine!
For Byzantine.
You convinced me, Nikola.
By saying that Osman has...
Father Gregor, you convinced me.
I will visit him tomorrow.
He'll deny it.
I'll understand it from his eyes.
The children of Christ will attack
when they hear about this.
-They'll burn your tribe.
-I know you to be smart.
Don't make me doubt that.
Control your anger.
Don't forget that the Latins
came for Jerusalem.
They killed their co-religionists,
the Orthodoxes.
They tyrannized there.
What do you want from me?
-To trust me.
-You? You!
To my devil?
I know that trust can't be gained
over a night.
But I say it tonight.
Know what I want.
Know it. Your eyes will
start to see the truth soon.
I will never trust you before
Christ comes down from the sky.
Do you understand?
This bed will do good.
Good night now.
Your eyes will spread fire.
Your hands will hold swords.
The enemies will lose their minds
for seeing you.
It will happen, right, son?
It will. It will.
Your grandfather Ertuğrul Ghazi
will watch over you.
Malhun Sultan.
You are ready.
You kept me waiting, Malhun Hatun.
Is it bad, my bey?
You were with Orhan.
Thank Allah.
-My bey.
-I'm listening, Malhun.
How is the love of a child?
It's great. Great.
Really is.
Thanks to you, I have a child.
Thank you.
Inshallah, you'll have
many children.
Come on. Let's not keep
the people waiting.
Behold!
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam.
Finally, his face is smiling.
Thank Allah.
So is yours, Bala.
It really does.
Come.
Enjoy it.
With the name of Allah.
-Boran.
-My bey.
Sing for us.
Alright, my bey.
We've done many charities.
Come, let's make peace.
Our horse is saddled.
Thanks to Allah.
We've done many charities.
We are reborn to be a river,
risen up to be a waterfall.
We looked at the sea.
Thanks to Allah.
We've done many charities.
Enemies came and left.
We survived.
We were at the doors of the lord.
We've grown like a sycamore.
Thanks to Allah.
We've done many charities.
The enemies came and left.
We survived.
We've done many charities.
The enemies came and left.
We survived.
Thanks to Allah.
Mashallah to my brother.
Thank you.
May Allah bless your hands.
Thank you, my bey.
Thank you.
Today, here, we gathered
for my son Orhan's 40th day.
My son in the bundle, Orhan...
and many other sons and daughters
like him, expect something from us.
What is it?
We'll teach them our traditions
and Islamic morals.
We exist from ancient times.
But whenever something bad happened
to us, it's because we forgot our customs.
It's because our morals got corrupted.
If we forget it, we turn into the enemy.
If we forget it, we'll lose...
before fighting in the field.
For this reason, it's all our
responsibility.
May Allah give us good
sons...
and good daughters.
-Amin.
How is your health, Pretty-eyed?
Does my child show its existence?
Wouldn't it?
It's already certain that it will be a
child of its father.
It started early.
What do you want it to be?
I want a daughter from Allah.
A daughter is a companion to the father.
Daughters love their fathers.
I want to comb her hair just like this.
I want her to set a table for me.
I want her to take your hands...
so that she can liven our tribe up.
Mount a horse, hold a sword, fight
a battle too.
That's for certain.
The mother is Bala Hatun.
Tell me. When do we tell
the people?
If you allow me, I want to tell
my father first.
-I want to tell him tomorrow.
-Alright.
Alright.
Orhan? Orhan!
Orhan! My son!
Orhan!
-Brother!
-Brother Orhan!
Orhan!
Orhan...
Orhan! My son!
Orhan! Orhan!
My son! No!
My son!
Orhan!
My son.
Bala?
Bala!
My son!
My son...
My Allah!
My son... My Orhan...
My son.
May Allah protect me.
With the ninety-nine names
of Allah...
who creates as he wants and
fulfills our hearts with faith.
Since the last year, we fought a lot.
But our enemies underestimated us.
Osman isn't our match, they said.
Since the last year...
they were answered many times
on the field.
Thank Allah.
Osman Bey, with the prosperity
of the last year...
all Turkmens are moving here.
-Our Bey is hope for them.
-Indeed.
The mountains are full with
Turkmen tents.
They are all our friends and relatives.
-They all are praying for you.
-Thank you.
Mashallah but I'm worried, Osman Bey.
Are you worried that we are a hope
for the Turkmens, Gündüz Bey?
You will hear what you say, Boran Alp.
This is the council.
You will think before speaking.
It's hard to understand the lovers,
Gündüz Bey.
Don't despise him.
Brother, tell us.
I will, brother.
Our Turkmen brothers are coming.
They are welcome.
But if we can't manage this
with our heads...
it will burn us.
You are right, brother.
Tell us what you heard.
Many warriors are acting on their
own on the borders.
They are having relationships
with the lords without us.
They even raid their lands.
Osman Bey, Byzantine schemes
never end.
Tomorrow, they can send one of those
strong warriors to face us.
Then, we'll have to spill
brothers' blood.
I heard it too. A warrior named
Turgut Alp...
already fights the lord of Harmankaya.
There are many like him, my bey.
Where are you?
My brother. Why did he
call me so suddenly?
-Don't you think it's strange, Cornelia?
-Maybe it's longing, my lady.
No, Cornelia. He would come
himself then.
Whatever it is, it must be important.
Everyone knows how much your brother
loves you. Even his enemies.
Cornelia. Is this why you
are anxious like this?
Who can hurt Kosses' sister?
We are guarded by many men.
We'll charge altogether.
You won't hesitate, you won't stumble.
If a horse gets afraid and flees...
-We need her alive.
-Alright, Turgut Bey!
We are under attack!
-My lady!
-Alright, stay calm.
Harmankaya's lord Michael Kosses'
dearie.
Welcome, Marie.
It's my order.
All new nomads will be visited.
Without my order, no one
mounts a horse.
Without an order, no one
wields a sword.
If my order gets
ignored...
they should be remembered of what
will happen.
Alright, my bey.
Thank you.
Alright.
My bey, Rogaros, the lord of
Bilecik is here. He wants audience.
Good. Good.
-What is this, brother?
-Something good.
Something good.
Welcome, Rogatus.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Harmankaya Castle
Lord Kosses!
The crew that was bringing your Mari...
...they were raided, Sir.
They kidnapped your sister.
The Bey of those Turks we imprisoned...
... Turgut Alp.
He kidnapped her!
In return for their worthless alps...
...my sister.
Is that so?
What will we do, Sir?
What will we do?
We will bring their world collapse
around them.
We will crucify them.
We will rip out their lungs.
We will rip out and take their lungs.
So, how will we take Mari back, Sir?
Who kills only one bird...
...with one stone...
... is either a fool...
...or a shepherd.
I am not that stupid Nikola.
I will play such a game to them that...
... with every step they take to
solve it...
...they will come closer to
becoming my prey.
Prepare a gift for Osman Bey.
We will pay him a visit.
Let's meet him already.
What shall we prepare for him?
Of course, the Turks' favorite.
Sure!
I am here to protect the friendship that
has been going on since Lord Leo...
...and your father Ertuğrul Gazi.
Good.
You did well, Lord Rogatus.
We want the same as well.
We know that as Tekfus Leo, you too come
from the Laskarid Dynasty.
This means you don't have a friendship
with the Emperor or the Lords.
You are right.
I hope our friendship will last for life.
I'd like to ask you something.
Father Gregor, who was supposed to be
under my protection...
...but unfortunately was taken from me.
I am looking for him.
We don't know who took him.
Do you have any information on the matter,
Osman Bey?
What would I do with a priest or an exarch,
Rogatus.
Why are you asking me this?
As you said earlier...
...I am not on good terms with the Emperor
or the Lords.
Father Gregor escaped the Emperor.
He was on the road to take refuge in me.
Those who want our help are
much important to us, Osman Bey.
Of course, those who want our help are
important to us too.
But the priest trusted you and
tried to take refuge.
I don't understand what does this have
to do with me.
Are you going to ask everyone escaping
you to me, Rogatus?
Father Gregor is my friend.
I will find him, Osman Bey.
Even though you are implying...
...you are blaming me.
However, you have many enemies.
Your dynasty is enough for
the other Lords.
Even for the Emperor.
What makes you an enemy to them,
makes you a friend to me.
We were friends with Lord Leo.
We'd like to stay friends with you too.
I hope, Osman Bey.
I hope.
May you be well.
They come to the tribe and ask about
a priest.
As if it is not enough, they blame us.
I told. I did.
This will not end for a while.
For a long while.
If you'll excuse me, Osman Bey.
What's done is done, brother.
It was supposed to happen and it did.
You keep cautious.
Keep an eye open for the priest.
As you command, my Bey.
You are smiling!
There is good news, obviously.
Really?
Thank goodness.
My Rabb saw me, heard my cries.
Made me a partner in the joy of
our Sare Valide, my Sheik.
Put out the fire in me.
I am going to be a mother, my Sheik.
Thanks to Allah!
''In the name of Allah, the merciful.''
“Allah is great and there is no god
but Allah.”
"Allah hears those who praise Him."
“Allah is great and there is no god
but Allah.”
"May the peace of Allah be upon you"
''In the name of Allah, the merciful.''
Thanks to Allah!
You garnished your waiting with patience,
my beautiful girl.
Allah granted you a child.
With no doubt, he is the one hearing
the prayers.
Even when I thought there was no remedy...
... your words would heal my heart,
my Sheik.
Now, you are also increasing my joy.
My Almighty Allah has tested you with
the test of his servants whom he loves.
You took the right road.
You put your Bey, your tribe and the world
of Islam first.
Your joy is your reward.
When should I announce it to the tribe,
my Sheik?
There is time, my dear.
There is time.
Turgut Bey Tribe
- Welcome, my Bey!
- Welcome Bey!
Kutay.
You will pay for this, you vile barbarian!
Barbarian?
You are this barbarian's guest until I get
my alps back, Rumelian beauty.
Lord Kosses.
Welcome.
Thank you, Alp.
I demand a meeting with Osman Bey.
He knows you were coming.
Alps!
Are you available, my Bey?
Come in.
Welcome, Mikhael Kosses.
What is it?
I brought a very precious Andalusian horse
for your son Orhan.
Like you say...
...the horse is a Turk's wing.
I hope you will like it, Osman Bey.
And your son may fly freely to wherever
he wants.
Thank you, thank you.
Lord Rogatus Laskaris came today.
He mentioned someone named Father Gregor.
I guess you came for him too.
Here you go.
I wish that was the case, Osman Bey.
Neither Rogatus nor Father Gregor...
I don't care about them, Osman Bey.
What is the matter, then?
My sister.
The convoy that was bringing my sister
Mari to me was raided.
Who did it was a Turkoman Bey.
Turgut Alp.
You must know him.
Is there a tradition of kidnapping women,
Osman Bey?
Do you have a tradition of intercepting
a defenseless woman...
... going home to her family?
Do you have a tradition of drawing
a sword...
...to those who don't have a sword,
Osman Bey?
Stop.
Be aware of your words, Kosses.
I am.
We know you as the leader of
all Turkmens in this area.
We know that no Turkmen around borders
can fly a bird without your knowledge.
Or do we know wrong?
You know right, Kosses.
I choose my friend and my enemy
myself.
And I choose with whom I will stay friends
or enemies.
They took my most precious from me.
I don't know even if she is alive or not.
I came here to ask for help from you.
If I am not aware of my words, the reason
is clear.
Whoever comes to my door and asks me
for help, especially for those in need...
... doesn't leave without getting
what he asked for.
Wait for my word.
I will bring your sister to you.
But...
... meanwhile, if you make a mistake...
... then you will incur my wrath.
God is my witness that my only wish is to
get my sister back safe and sound.
You are as much as they say.
May God protect you.
- Alps!
- My Bey.
Make the preparations.
Let's go to Turgut Alp.
Let's meet him.
Let's find out why he kidnapped Kosses'
sister Mari.
Let's see what is behind this.
- As you command, Bey!
- As you command, my Bey!
Turgut Bey Tribe
Destur, Hatun!
You must be hungry.
Come on, eat.
Do you want to poison us?
Don't be afraid.
Snake! Snake!
Not me but...
...someone else was going to poison you.
You wait for gratitude.
I will never be grateful to a barbarian
like you who treats women like this!
Look, woman!
My problem is not with you.
Your brother Kosses imprisoned my alps.
If your brother gives my alps back
safe and sound...
...you can get out of here.
My brother Kosses will make you pay
for this!
Let him do so.
Turgut Bey Tribe
Hand holds the sword, Kutan.
The arm connects the hand to the body.
You are my right arm.
You won't go to give this news.
Kosses' wound is deep.
He will try to attack at every chance.
Serhat!
To Lord Kosses.
Turgut Alp!
It's me!
Who is asking?
The son of Ertuğrul Gazi, Bey of
the Kayı tribe, Osman Bey.
Make way to your Osman Bey, alps!
- Selamun Aleyküm.
-Aleyküm Selam.
Welcome.
The girl you kidnapped, Mari.
Her brother, Lord of Harmankaya Mikhael
Kosses came to me.
He wants his sister.
Osman Bey.
We know your name, your bravery,
and your power well.
Just as you do all you do to protect
your tribe...
...I do the same.
Mikhael Kosses has my alps.
I won't give Mari back until I see my alps
back in the tribe.
Neither to you, Osman Bey, nor to anyone
else.
If you know my name and bravery,
then you must also know...
... you must trust my word, Turgut Alp.
Give Mari to me.
And I will take your alps back and give
them back to you.
Therefore, I will be an intermediary in
the trade you will make anyway.
-Kutan, bring the girls.
-As you command, my Bey.
Osman Bey will take you to your brother
Kosses.
But tell him.
We will meet him one day.
I will be there to watch when
that day comes.
Come on, leave.
You did the right thing.
Osman Bey!
I would like to know you as I did
before we met.
A man of his word.
Don't worry!
We know you as one of us.
You know us as you please.
You will have your alps back as soon as
possible.
-Boran.
-Yes, my Bey?
Take Mari.
And take back the alps of Turgut Alp.
-But remain cautious.
-As you command, my Bey.
Harmankaya Castle
But we guaranteed our job.
Forefinger...
... and thumb.
These hands can no longer hold a sword
or use a bow.
You really guaranteed it, Sir.
But my fear is that, as you know, they
have Mari.
When he sees them like this--
Of course, Osman Bey will come to us
with that request.
He will say ''I brought you your sister
but Turgut also wants his alps back.''.
And we won't upset him.
We will give them back.
Just with a little missing.
Sir, one of Osman Bey's alps, Boran Alp
came.
Your sister is with him, Sir.
Osman Bey kept his promise quicker than
I expected.
What will we do now, Master Gregor?
How long will we stay here?
We won't be wasting time, Andreas.
We will find a way to inform
Lord Rogatus.
We can't get out of here without him.
-Andreas, the door.
-Of course, Sir.
Are you well?
It is well.
We will live, Andreas.
We will live and get rid of Osman for the
trust we are carrying.
Brother!
Are you alright?
Come here.
I owe Osman Bey for bringing my sister
to me safe and sound.
We brought your sister
to you safe and sound.
Now give us Turgut Bey's alps safe and
sound.
You brought me my most precious.
Nestor, set the imprisoned Turks free
immediately.
Come on, my brothers!
Come on!
Brothers!
Stay calm.
What is this, Tekfus Kosses?
Each bow they stretched cost the life
of one of my soldiers.
I took two fingers from them for each
life they took.
I think it is enough.
Right?
Would you be satisfied with less,
Boran Alp?
Send my gratitude to Osman Bey.
Come on, have a safe trip.
Mari.
I remembered the past. How hard we tried
to weave various rugs with Hayme Ana.
Poverty on one side,
the enemy on the other...
Though, Turk's enemies never cease
to exist.
Look, thankfully now we have
a great tribe.
And these eyes had a chance to see
my Orhan.
May Allah raise him with his mother
and father, my dear.
May Allah grant him to be a son
worthy of his ancestors.
Amen, mother.
- Tell me, where is my Orhan? How's he?
- He is fine, thank Allah.
He's asleep.
He'll be a good kid.
My daughter, thank Allah we have an heir.
Inshallah you will have more children.
Inshallah, mother.
Selcan mother, I am curious
about something.
You are an experienced woman.
I always wondered whether my child
would be a girl or a boy.
Some say...
if you have a higher tummy, it will be
a girl...
if you have a lower tummy, it
will be a boy.
Yes, mine was low.
Yes but it's not always true.
They also say that if you
crave sweets, it's a boy...
and if you crave sour
food, it's a girl.
- Have a nice day, Hatuns.
- Thank you, Bala Hatun.
- Welcome, Bala.
- Thank you, Selcan mother.
Welcome, Bala Hatun.
Where are you coming from?
I have visited my father.
- Inshallah he's fine and healthy.
- Yes, thank Allah.
I haven't seen you anywhere in the tent.
What happened?
Beys are at
the war, Hatuns are in the tent.
I am so happy to see you like that.
My daughters.
Mashallah.
Turkmens trust Osman.
He should be happy to gain their trust.
He should feel comfortable in his tent.
Don't be angry towards me for what I said.
Be nice to each other.
People will say lots of things if they
see you unhappy.
Be protective over each other.
May your sisterhood be infinite.
- Thank you, mother.
I'll wander around. Have a nice day.
- Have a nice day, Hatuns.
- Thank you, Selcan Hatun.
Are you pregnant?
What?
How do you know?
- Is it true?
- Who told you that?
I had a dream.
You were holding a baby. Tell me.
Is it true?
Mashallah. It's a miracle.
The miracle of Allah.
- It'll be a comrade to my Orhan.
- Inshallah.
I wanted to be sure. That's why I didn't
tell anyone.
Thank Allah.
Tell me, what do you crave?
When I was pregnant, I craved sweets.
What do you want?
Sweet food or sour food?
Thank you, Malhun Hatun.
I don't crave anything.
It's our secret, right?
Don't tell anyone.
I want to be sure first.
- Then we'll tell everyone.
- I know, Bala Hatun.
Don't worry, it's our secret.
It's a trap!
Brothers, come on!
Be careful, Alps!
Come on, brothers!
Brilliant.
However, you should wear it to
see how brilliant it is.
I want you to wear this.
If you let me.
You have been with
me for a long time, Feodor.
I always loved tailoring.
This is brilliant.
Very beautiful.
Here it is!
Wait, this part looks.. as if...
no, no...
this part...
this shoulder...
looks bad.
If...
I was not from a noble family...
and I was not a Lord in Bithynia...
I would be a tailor.
However, it can't always happen.
I hope you understand me.
I can't...
Next time...
do what duty I give to you.
Because of your silliness...
we don't know where Father Gregor is.
Mashallah, my son.
I'm so happy for you, Osman Bey.
What, Malhun Hatun?
Bala Hatun is pregnant. My Orhan
will have a sibling.
Thank you.
It's a miracle.
My Allah made Bala happy.
Every pray has an answer.
Come here.
I want to talk to you about it.
You have come to me.
We have our Orhan now.
You have become my Hatun.
You have become my comrade.
You will always be important to me.
Don't be sad.
I know it's hard.
Don't worry...
my Allah will make you
happy with our Orhan.
Thank you, my Bey.
You have cured my troubles.
My Orhan.
They're here.
Boran.
Bey.
What happened?
Who did this?
We dropped Mari and set off.
Then we got ambushed.
Who did this?
Who?
Rogatus.
Rogatus' dog.
Bring Karayel, Göktuğ.
Eyvallah (Okay), my Bey.
We'll take his relics...
to Turgut Bey.
Bury the dead..
Dig the graves of the traitors.
Your command, my Bey.
My Bey.
Karayel.
Come on, brothers.
Karayel!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com